New York State Governor's Committee on the State Employees' Retirement System Papers 5681
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State Governor's Committee on the State Employees' Retirement System Papers
1955-1969
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State Governor's Committee on the State Employees' Retirement System
5681
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5689670
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 03, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 25, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5842: David G. Moore Additional Papers
New York (State).; New York (State). Governors Committee on the State Employees' Retirement System.
5689670
- Mortality by Occupation and Cause of Death, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Union Related Books, Miscellaneous, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- North Carolina - Material Pursuit Driving, 1958-1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Union Fire Fighters, Misc., 1963-1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence - in, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- SSA - D1 -DSB, 1961-1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Correspondence - out, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Comments on Policemen and Firemen - Kenneth Altman, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- AMA Material, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- National Safety Council Material, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Federal Employee Injury Rates, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Report of the Governor's Committee on The State Employee's Retirement System, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Misc. Material, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Health Statistics - U.S. - Health Statistics - N.Y.S., 1957-1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- NYC Police Annual Reports 1960-1966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- NYC Fire Dept. Material, 1963-1967 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Fire Department Annual Reports City of New York, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- FDNY Annual Report 1964 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- BLS - Injury Reports, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Toronto Fire Dept. Material Dr. Robert E. Ralph, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Respiratory Hazards of Fire Fighting, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Manpower Projection - 10 years March, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Quotes (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Bibliography (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Activities (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Notes, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Time and Expense Material (Box 1, Folder 27)
- New York Misc., 1963-1967 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Paper (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Tables, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 30)